Guide to the United Automobile Workers of America, District 65 Records WAG 006
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VII: Shop Files, 1937-1971 (Box 68 - 154)
  - GR-HE
    - Haber & Fink, 1947-1949 (Box 95, Folder 8-9)
    - Hale-Nass Corp, 1942-1956 (Box 95, Folder 10-12)
    - Robert Hall, 1950 (Box 95, Folder 13)
    - Hampden Sales Associates, 1940-1950 (Box 95, Folder 14-15)
    - Handcraft Manufacturing (includes leaflet in Spanish and shop photo), 1957-1958 (Box 95, Folder 16-18)
    - Harlem Crockery, 1948-1949 (Box 95, Folder 19-20)
    - Hartford Textile (includes strike preparations), 1946-1953 (Box 95, Folder 21-25)
    - Oscar Hayman, 1940-1948 (Box 95, Folder 26-27)
    - Hecht and Biern, 1946-1968 (Box 95, Folder 28-29)
    - S.W. Heim, 1941-1959 (Box 95, Folder 30)
    - Heinsheimer Bros (see Box 96), 1942-1946 (Box 95, Folder 31)
  - HE-HO
    - Heinsheimer Bros (see Box 96--includes newspaper with letter by employer on anti-Semitism), 1942-1946 (Box 96, Folder 1-2)
    - S. W. Heim Co, 1941-1960 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Herald Knitwear, 1946 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Herman Tifford's Interiors--Tifford's Furniture, 1950-1968 (Box 96, Folder 5-6)
    - Hill Lalin, 1940-1953 (Box 96, Folder 7-9)
    - H.I.S. Enameling, 1950-1957 (Box 96, Folder 10-11)
    - Hodes-Daniels, 1959-1963 (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - Home for the Aged, 1950-1951 (Box 96, Folder 13-15)
    - Hooven Letter Co. (includes leaflets), 1944-1959 (Box 96, Folder 16-21)
    - Hoover Co (includes leaflets), 1956-1957 (Box 96, Folder 22-23)
    - Hopp Press (includes leaflets), 1965-1966 (Box 96, Folder 24-25)
  - HA-IN
    - Hafner & Stecher, Virginia (includes leaflets), 1969 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Hi-Grade Gas Range, Good Neighbor, 1947-1964 (Box 97, Folder 2-3)
    - Hopkins Transfer & Storage, S. Carolina (includes leaflets), 1969-1970 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - L & W Horowitz, 1939-1953 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Horowitz - Margareten, 1940-1953 (Box 97, Folder 6-7)
    - Hub Vacuum, 1941-1951 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Hudson Corrugated Carton (AFL #217), 1941-1950 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - Hughes Direct Mail, 1961 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Hyko China, 1949-1952 (Box 97, Folder 11-12)
    - I & B Textile, 1958-1959 (Box 97, Folder 13)
    - Illustrated Soap, 1941-1953 (Box 97, Folder 14)
    - Ideal Shoe, 1951-1952 (Box 97, Folder 15)
    - Imperial Container--Corrugated, 1948-1959 (Box 97, Folder 16-17)
    - Independent Quilting, 1941-1948 (Box 97, Folder 18-19)
    - Industrial Corrugated--leaflet only, undated (Box 97, Folder 20)
    - Inlays Inc--Dental, 1957-1966 (Box 97, Folder 21)
    - Interlining Distributors, 1940-1948 (Box 97, Folder 22)
    - Grievances, Direct Mail, Hoover, Gray--Frank Patten, 1960-1961 (Box 97, Folder 23)
    - Horowitz Brothers & Margreten, 1943-1968 (Box 97, Folder 24-25)
    - Interlining Distributors Association, 1945-1954 (Box 97, Folder 26)
  - IN-JA
    - International Mutoscope, 1946-1956 (Box 98, Folder 1-3)
    - Interscience Publications, 1949-1959 (Box 98, Folder 4-7)
    - Institute of Pacific Relations, 1947-1948 (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - J. C. Penney, 1946 (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - J. P. Stevens, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - J. N. T. Manufacturing, 1949-1959 (Box 98, Folder 11-13)
    - Jarmel-Roth, 1950-1957 (Box 98, Folder 14-15)
  - JA-JE
    - Jaymar Knitwear, 1959-1963 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Lion Fabrics (includes Salesmen's Declaration of Independence), 1959 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - O.B. Johnson, various grievances of Frank Patten, 1959-1961 (Box 99, Folder 3-9)
    - Jokay Manufacturing, 1950-1960 (Box 99, Folder 10-11)
    - Jomill Fabrics, 1960 (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - Jonas Shoppes, 1949-1955 (Box 99, Folder 13-18)
    - Joroco Silk, 1941-1950 (Box 99, Folder 19-20)
    - Josephson Manufacturing (includes leaflets), 1942-1950 (Box 99, Folder 21-30)
    - Fabrics by Joyce, 1963 (Box 99, Folder 31-32)
    - Jewish Social Service Assn. (UOPWA), 1941-1947 (Box 99, Folder 33)
  - K-KF
    - K & K Hats, 1946-1965 (Box 100, Folder 1-2)
    - K & W Paper (includes leaflets), 1946-1952 (Box 100, Folder 3-4)
    - Kandell Inc (includes leaflets, strike preps), 1947-1952 (Box 100, Folder 5-7)
    - Katz Toy Co, 1942-1952 (Box 100, Folder 8-9)
    - Kauffman & Ruderman, 1938-1945 (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - Kehoe Machine Co, 1948-1949 (Box 100, Folder 11-12)
    - Max Keller, 1941-1952 (Box 100, Folder 13)
    - Keller Mailing, 1953-1960 (Box 100, Folder 14-15)
    - Kent Corrugated, 1945-1948 (Box 100, Folder 16)
    - Kenville Fabrics, 1947-1954 (Box 100, Folder 17)
    - J. Kfares, 1954-1958 (Box 100, Folder 18-19)
  - KI-KL
    - King Sol - Syncro (includes leaflets), 1946-1948 (Box 101, Folder 1-3)
    - Kings County Supply Co, 1937-1950 (Box 101, Folder 4-5)
    - Ben Kirschenbaum, 1941-1959 (Box 101, Folder 6-8)
    - Kirsch Blacher (Shoe), 1941-1960 (Box 101, Folder 9-10)
    - B. Kittay & Sons, 1940-1960 (Box 101, Folder 11-18)
    - Klaber Bros, 1948-1959 (Box 101, Folder 19-26)
    - D. Emil Klein (see Box 102), 1942-1953 (Box 101, Folder 27)
  - KL-KR
    - D. Emil Klein (see Box 101), 1942-1953 (Box 102, Folder 1-2)
    - Knitwear Employers' Association, 1944-1963 (Box 102, Folder 3-5)
    - Alfred Knopf, 1947-1951 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Kohler Allweil, 1943-1946 (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Kolip Bag, 1948-1966 (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - Koler Cigar, 1947-1957 (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Korner Fabrics, 1955-1962 (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - E.J. Korvette, 1957 (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - Kosover & Radin, 1939-1961 (Box 102, Folder 12-13)
    - Sidmar Krabro--Krabro Fabrics, 1940-1960 (Box 102, Folder 14-15)
    - Kramer Jewelry, 1949 (Box 102, Folder 16)
    - Max Kramer & Son, 1952-1965 (Box 102, Folder 17-18)
  - JE-LA
    - Jersey Carpet Corp, 1957-1958 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Krassnoff Dental, 1960 (Box 103, Folder 2-3)
    - Kraut Textile, 1953-1962 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Kresge--New Jersey, 1950 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - L & B Hosiery, 1940-1949 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Lamar Zipper, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Lampcraft Studios, Inc, 1955-1960 (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Lane Bryant (extensive documentation of UOPWA shop, includes strike press clippings, leaflets & newsletters, materials pertaining to 1948-1951 disaffiliation campaign)(see Box 104), 1941-1951 (Box 103, Folder 9-19)
  - LA-LE
    - Lane Bryant (UOPWA disaffiliation) (see Box 103), 1949-1951 (Box 104, Folder 1-2)
    - Laura Modes, 1962 (Box 104, Folder 3-4)
    - Leather Coating Corp, 1968-1969 (Box 104, Folder 5-6)
    - Lee Leather, 1945-1951 (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Legal Aid, 1973 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Lerner Shops, 1937-1950 (Box 104, Folder 9-30)
  - LE-LI
    - Leroy Foods (includes strike preps), 1946-1950 (Box 105, Folder 1-3)
    - Phillip Leventhal & Sons, 1938-1952 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Bert Levi, 1950-1957 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - J. Levine, 1950 (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Rubin Levine, 1942-1944 (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - H. Levinson, 1946-1964 (Box 105, Folder 8-9)
    - Morris Levinson, 1941-1953 (Box 105, Folder 10-11)
    - I. Levitsky, 1941-1962 (Box 105, Folder 12-14)
    - Levy Shoe, 1942-1957 (Box 105, Folder 15)
    - Lily of France (includes strike preps), 1950-1951 (Box 105, Folder 16-17)
    - Lincoln Letter Service, 1960-1963 (Box 105, Folder 18-19)
    - S. Lipp, 1947-1966 (Box 105, Folder 20)
    - D. Lisner Giftware, 1937-1955 (Box 105, Folder 21-24)
    - Lite Manufacturing (see Box 106), 1944-1951 (Box 105, Folder 25-16)
  - LI-LO
    - Lite Manufacturing (see Box 105), 1944-1955 (Box 106, Folder 1-4)
    - Livingston Bros., 1948-1958 (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - London Records, 1950-1959 (Box 106, Folder 6-14)
    - London Gramophone (includes support for NAACP), 1949-1951 (Box 106, Folder 15)
    - Longchamps Fabrics, 1941-1968 (Box 106, Folder 16-17)
  - LO-LU
    - Lord & Taylor (includes leaflets), 1949-1951 (Box 107, Folder 1-2)
    - Lowy Imports, 1958-1964 (Box 107, Folder 3-4)
    - Michael Lowy, 1941-1951 (Box 107, Folder 5-6)
    - Dr. Lunenfeld Dental (includes leaflets), 1944-1951 (Box 107, Folder 7-9)
    - L. Luria & Son, 1954-1961 (Box 107, Folder 10-30)
  - M-MAI
    - M & F Tag Stringing (includes Jewelry Workers dispute), 1954 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - M. J. Levy, 1956-1962 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - M & L Sales, 1946-1950 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - M & M Lumber, 1946-1953 (Box 108, Folder 4-5)
    - M & M Shoe Co, 1957-1958 (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - M & M Underwear, 1946-1962 (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - M & R Plastics, 1954 (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - Macrose Lumber, Nassau Terminal, 1949 (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - Madison Shoe, 1941-1957 (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - Madison Wisconsin, University Bookstore Employees, 1971 (Box 108, Folder 11)
    - Madisonit, 1946-1948 (Box 108, Folder 12)
    - Mado Manufacturing, 1960-1965 (Box 108, Folder 13-14)
    - Magid & Eisen, 1941-1945 (Box 108, Folder 15)
    - Magna Products, 1946-1960 (Box 108, Folder 16-20)
    - Magram Hardware, 1945 (Box 108, Folder 21)
    - Maharam's, undated (Box 108, Folder 22-23)
    - Maidenform (includes peace activism, red-baiting and leaflets), 1944-1951 (Box 108, Folder 24-26)
    - Mailers Equipment, undated (Box 108, Folder 27)
    - Mailings Inc, 1959-1961 (Box 108, Folder 28-37)
    - Maillard Textile, 1949-1963 (Box 108, Folder 38)
    - Mailograph, Direct Mail, 1958-1963 (Box 108, Folder 39)
  - MAJ-MAN
    - Majestic Merchandise, 1952-1963 (Box 109, Folder 1-2)
    - Majestic Trimming, 1948-1964 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Major Merchandise, 1945-1965 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Makegood Manufacturing, 1941-1962 (Box 109, Folder 5-8)
    - Makel Textile, 1951-1966 (Box 109, Folder 9)
    - A. Malamod & Sons, 1967-1968 (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - Mallary Furniture, 1957 (Box 109, Folder 11)
    - Malt Distate (Confectionary Workers #362, AFL), 1948 (Box 109, Folder 12)
    - Mamaroneck TV Stores, 1954-1960 (Box 109, Folder 13-14)
    - Manalwill, 1951-1964 (Box 109, Folder 15)
    - Manart Textile, 1951-1966 (Box 109, Folder 16-17)
    - Mandee Fabrics, 1944-1959 (Box 109, Folder 18)
    - Mandel Bag, 1945-1948 (Box 109, Folder 19)
    - M. Mandell, 1940-1948 (Box 109, Folder 20)
    - Max Mandel Laces, 1949-1959 (Box 109, Folder 21-23)
    - Mandel Shoe Company, 1944-1947 (Box 109, Folder 24)
    - Mandell Platic Buttons, 1949 (Box 109, Folder 25)
    - Manhattan Corrugated, 1941-1949 (Box 109, Folder 26)
    - Manhattan Direct Mail, 1969 (Box 109, Folder 27)
    - Manhattan Glove & Notion, 1940-1958 (Box 109, Folder 28-29)
    - Manhattan Lumber Co (includes strike materials), 1948-1954 (Box 109, Folder 30-31)
  - MAN-MAR
    - Manhattan Novelty, 1941-1958 (Box 110, Folder 1-3)
    - Manhattan Pad & Table, 1958 (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - Manhattan Stationery, 1949 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Manhattan Quilting, 1951-1959 (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Manhattanville Neighborhood Center, 1949 (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - Manheim Shoe, 1968 (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - Mangel Shoe, 1950 (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - Ben Mann Fabrics, 1951-1954 (Box 110, Folder 10)
    - Robert Mann Shoe, 1949-1962 (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - Manon Freres (includes Chemical Workers #121), 1941-1949 (Box 110, Folder 12)
    - Mansfield Lumber, 1949-1954 (Box 110, Folder 13)
    - Mansol Manufacturing, 1952 (Box 110, Folder 14)
    - Manor Manufacturing, 1940-1947 (Box 110, Folder 15-18)
    - Manufacturers Container, 1943-1960 (Box 110, Folder 19-20)
    - Maple Knitwear, 1941 (Box 110, Folder 21)
    - Maradel (formerly Theon) (includes steward book), 1960-1965 (Box 110, Folder 22-23)
    - Morris Marantz, 1946-1948 (Box 110, Folder 24)
    - Ben Marbach, 1944-1956 (Box 110, Folder 25)
    - Marboro Books, 1956-1961 (Box 110, Folder 26)
    - Marcy Lumber, 1950-1954 (Box 110, Folder 27)
    - Marda Trucking, 1960-1962 (Box 110, Folder 28)
  - MAR-MAS
    - Marder & Dombrow, 1948-1950 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Mardi Fabrics, 1941-1948 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Margold Textiles, 1948-1956 (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Philip Margulies, 1941-1947 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Marietta Silk, 1942-1968 (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Marin & Stern Dental, 1941-1958 (Box 111, Folder 6-7)
    - Marine Bros, 1950 (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - Marion Shoe, 1941-1945 (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - T. Mark Furniture, 1967 (Box 111, Folder 10)
    - Mark Woolen, 1951-1957 (Box 111, Folder 11)
    - Markay Fabrics, 1949-1963 (Box 111, Folder 12)
    - Markell & Sons, 1954 (Box 111, Folder 13)
    - I. Markowitz & Sons, 1945-1961 (Box 111, Folder 14)
    - S. Marks Dental Lab, 1941-1951 (Box 111, Folder 15)
    - Marks & Rosenfeld, 1946-1948 (Box 111, Folder 16)
    - Marlene Fabrics, 1953-1954 (Box 111, Folder 17)
    - Marlboro Fabrics, 1941-1963 (Box 111, Folder 18-20)
    - Marlin Manufacturing, 1946-1947 (Box 111, Folder 21)
    - Marmax, 1950 (Box 111, Folder 22)
    - Mar Ral Plastics, 1954 (Box 111, Folder 23)
    - Marriello Fabrics, 1960 (Box 111, Folder 24)
    - Martin Processing, 1956 (Box 111, Folder 25)
    - Martins Supplies Inc, 1953-1954 (Box 111, Folder 26)
    - Marshalls (includes materials on Strauss Stores), 1953 (Box 111, Folder 27)
    - Maryland Rayon Mills, 1941-1966 (Box 111, Folder 28-29)
    - Marzani Munsell, 1961-1967 (Box 111, Folder 30)
    - Mastercraft Toy (includes strike materials), 1952-1959 (Box 111, Folder 31)
    - Masters Westchester, 1956-1958 (Box 111, Folder 32)
    - Mastro Plastics (includes leaflets in Spanish, clash with Carpenters AFL #3127), 1950-1959 (Box 111, Folder 33-34)
  - MAU-MEN
    - Mautner (includes clash with AFL #299), 1952 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - May Company, 1953 (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - May Knitting, 1940-1949 (Box 112, Folder 3-4)
    - Wm F. Mayer, 1950 (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Mayer Lumber, 1950-1953 (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - Mayerson & Singer, 1956-1959 (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - Maxwell & Phillips, 1952 (Box 112, Folder 8)
    - McAdams Advertising, 1951 (Box 112, Folder 9)
    - McCall's Patterns, 1965 (Box 112, Folder 10)
    - McFab Knitting Mills, 1960-1964 (Box 112, Folder 11)
    - McGrath Shoe, 1949 (Box 112, Folder 12)
    - O. E. McIntyre, 1956 (Box 112, Folder 13)
    - McKenna Leather Co, 1949 (Box 112, Folder 14)
    - McLaird, Inc, 1950-1963 (Box 112, Folder 15)
    - MacLaren Sportswear, 1950 (Box 112, Folder 16-17)
    - MacLeavy, 1957-1964 (Box 112, Folder 18)
    - Meadtex, undated (Box 112, Folder 19)
    - Meadows Service, 1950-1962 (Box 112, Folder 20)
    - Medico Stationary, 1965 (Box 112, Folder 21)
    - Melba Food, 1965 (Box 112, Folder 22)
    - Melburt, 1938-1966 (Box 112, Folder 23-25)
    - Melendie Cigars, 1945-1952 (Box 112, Folder 26)
    - J. A. Melnick Lumber, 1947-1954 (Box 112, Folder 27-28)
    - Melodie Textile, 1950-1957 (Box 112, Folder 29)
    - Meltex Inc, 1955 (Box 112, Folder 30)
    - Meltzer & Griffel, 1949-1952 (Box 112, Folder 31)
    - Meltzer & Kraploff, 1939-1950 (Box 112, Folder 32)
    - Menczer Jewelry, 1945-1950 (Box 112, Folder 33)
    - Mendelson Fiering & Horowitz, 1942-1963 (Box 112, Folder 34)
    - Mendelson Jewelry Harlew, 1945 (Box 112, Folder 35-36)
    - Menke Lieberman, 1965 (Box 112, Folder 37)
  - MEN-MER
    - Menters Credit, 1948-1964 (Box 113, Folder 1-4)
    - Bernstein Menton & Fox, 1944-1949 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Merber Woolen, 1949-1954 (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - D & A Merchandise, 1951 (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - N.Y. Merchandise, 1956-1959 (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - Merchant Oversea, 1950 (Box 113, Folder 9)
    - Merchants Importing Millinery, 1962 (Box 113, Folder 10)
    - Mercury Woolen, 1949-1954 (Box 113, Folder 11)
    - Meridee Cottons, 1949-1955 (Box 113, Folder 12)
    - Merit Paint, 1943-1960 (Box 113, Folder 13-14)
    - Merit Textile, 1956-1958 (Box 113, Folder 15)
    - Meritex Ribbon-Needle Processing, 1953-1956 (Box 113, Folder 16)
    - Mern's Inc, 1949-1953 (Box 113, Folder 17)
    - Merrit Tex, 1965 (Box 113, Folder 18)
    - Merriweather Knit, 1949-1960 (Box 113, Folder 19-21)
    - Meryle Publishing, 1941-1948 (Box 113, Folder 22-25)
    - Messing Knit, 1946-1949 (Box 113, Folder 26-27)
    - Metal Purchasing Co, 1950 (Box 113, Folder 28)
    - Metal Craft Lab, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 29)
    - Metro Container, 1947-1960 (Box 113, Folder 30-31)
    - Merchant Suppliers, 1959 (Box 113, Folder 32)
  - MET
    - Metro Envelope, 1951 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Metro Export, 1965 (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - Metro Hosiery, 1943-1962 (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Metro Kingdom Corp, 1950-1958 (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Metro Music & Sport Shop, 1945-1947 (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Metro Veiling, 1943-1946 (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Metropolitan Container Council, 1941-1949 (Box 114, Folder 7-8)
    - Metropolitan Displaymen's Association, 1939-1949 (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - Metropolitan Lumber, 1946-1952 (Box 114, Folder 10-11)
    - Metropolitan News Co, 1959-1961 (Box 114, Folder 12)
    - Metropolitan Offset, 1963 (Box 114, Folder 13)
    - Metropolitan Pickle Works, 1953 (Box 114, Folder 14)
    - Metropolitan Thread, 1948-1951 (Box 114, Folder 15)
    - Metropolitan Sacks, 1944-1946 (Box 114, Folder 16-17)
    - Meyers Millbrand, 1949 (Box 114, Folder 18)
    - Micas Cigar Factory, 1949-1960 (Box 114, Folder 19)
    - Michael Press, 1955-1956 (Box 114, Folder 20)
    - Joseph Michaelover, 1946-1952 (Box 114, Folder 21)
    - Ernest J. Michel, 1961-1965 (Box 114, Folder 22)
    - Mickey Fabrics, 1951-1953 (Box 114, Folder 23)
    - Middleton Card Company, 1965-1967 (Box 114, Folder 24)
    - Midland Color and Chemical Company, 1940-1949 (Box 114, Folder 25)
    - Midland Shoe, 1941-1949 (Box 114, Folder 26)
    - MidTex Fabrics, 1955 (Box 114, Folder 27)
    - Midtown Letter, 1957 (Box 114, Folder 28)
    - Milcore, 1954 (Box 114, Folder 29)
    - Milgram, 1948-1957 (Box 114, Folder 30)
    - Milgrims, 1953-1960 (Box 114, Folder 31)
    - Howard Miles Textile, 1955 (Box 114, Folder 32)
    - Miles Shoe, 1939-1949 (Box 114, Folder 33-34)
    - Mill End Imports, 1960-1961 (Box 114, Folder 35)
    - Mill Factors, 1965 (Box 114, Folder 36)
    - Metro Envelope (includes constitution and by-laws of the 'Independent Envelope Workers Union), 1962 (Box 114, Folder 37)
  - MIL-MIS
    - Mill Knit (strike materials), 1946-1948 (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Mill Lumber Company, 1948-1954 (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Millinery Ready to Wear (includes AFL #90 raid), 1943 (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - Miller Fabrics, 1947-1954 (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Miller Harness Company, 1965 (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - Miller Products, 1951-1955 (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - Miller Rubber, 1949-1957 (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - Miller Service, 1968 (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - Miller Shoe -- Asher Shoe, 1947-1952 (Box 115, Folder 9)
    - Millinery Suppliers & Importers Ass'n, 1940-1946 (Box 115, Folder 10)
    - Joint Millinery Data, 1942 (Box 115, Folder 11)
    - Milliner Jobbers, 1940-1947 (Box 115, Folder 12-14)
    - Miscellaneous Millinery & Knit, 1944-1948 (Box 115, Folder 15-16)
    - Mills Sales Co, 1961 (Box 115, Folder 17)
    - Milo Radio & Electronics, 1948 (Box 115, Folder 18)
    - Mitchell Mogal, 1963-1966 (Box 115, Folder 19)
    - Miltex Fabrics, 1963-1965 (Box 115, Folder 20)
    - Milton Hollander, 1948-1952 (Box 115, Folder 21)
    - Milton Silk, 1941-1948 (Box 115, Folder 22)
    - Milson Sales Corp, 1959 (Box 115, Folder 23)
    - Milwa Textile, 1950 (Box 115, Folder 24-25)
    - Minneapolis Museum, 1971 (Box 115, Folder 26)
    - Minute Men Radio & Appliance, 1946-1949 (Box 115, Folder 27)
    - Miracle Fabrics, 1953-1962 (Box 115, Folder 28)
    - Miron Lumber, 1945-1953 (Box 115, Folder 29)
    - Sam Mischel, 1944-1953 (Box 115, Folder 30)
    - Percy Mishkoff, 1940-1947 (Box 115, Folder 31)
    - Miss Swank, 1943-1954 (Box 115, Folder 32-33)
  - MIT-MOR
    - Mitteldorfer Straus, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Mitten Toys, 1950 (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Mizzy Inc (Dental), 1945-1953 (Box 116, Folder 3-4)
    - Modell's Since 1899, 1949-1951 (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - Henry Modell's, 1941-1955 (Box 116, Folder 6-12)
    - Modern Aljac, 1944-1951 (Box 116, Folder 13-17)
    - Modern Radio & Appliance, 1949 (Box 116, Folder 18)
    - Modern Television, 1949 (Box 116, Folder 19)
    - Modern Quilting, 1949 (Box 116, Folder 20)
    - Mohawk Sales, 1949-1954 (Box 116, Folder 21-22)
    - Mojud Hosiery, 1950 (Box 116, Folder 23)
    - Monarch Saphin, 1950 (Box 116, Folder 24)
    - Monroe Mill Supply, 1948-1950 (Box 116, Folder 25)
    - Monroe Textile, 1956-1960 (Box 116, Folder 26)
    - Montalbano Cigar Store, 1951 (Box 116, Folder 27)
    - Montauk Paint, 1945-1951 (Box 116, Folder 28-29)
    - Jose Morales (local 273), 1947-1954 (Box 116, Folder 30-31)
    - Morlee Fabrics, 1941-1950 (Box 116, Folder 32)
    - Morris Park Lumber, 1950-1953 (Box 116, Folder 33)
  - MOS-NOR
    - A. Mosbacher, 1955 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Moskin Stores, 1946-1961 (Box 117, Folder 2-3)
    - Moskowitz Cigar Stores, 1949-1956 (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - Moss & Associates, 1953-1965 (Box 117, Folder 5-6)
    - Moss Fabrics, 1959-1961 (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - A. Mossbacker & Sons, 1958-1961 (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - Mucon Corporation, 1952-1965 (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - Muriette Fabrics, 1949-1952 (Box 117, Folder 10)
    - Muriel Silk, 1943-1962 (Box 117, Folder 11)
    - Murray Miller, 1947-1951 (Box 117, Folder 12-13)
    - Murray Distributors, 1953 (Box 117, Folder 14)
    - Murral Fabrics, 1952-1963 (Box 117, Folder 15)
    - Murray Textile, 1948-1949 (Box 117, Folder 16)
    - Music Hall Jewelers, 1950-1953 (Box 117, Folder 17)
    - The Music Room, 1948 (Box 117, Folder 18)
    - Mutual Shoe Company, 1949-1962 (Box 117, Folder 19)
    - Mutual Lumber, 1950-1953 (Box 117, Folder 20)
    - Muzak, undated (Box 117, Folder 21)
    - Names Unlimited, 1950-1954 (Box 117, Folder 22)
    - National Shoes, 1946-1960 (Box 117, Folder 23-25)
    - New York Loose Leaf, 1953-1955 (Box 117, Folder 26)
    - Victor S. Noerdlinger, 1965 (Box 117, Folder 27)
    - Normandie Press, 1951 (Box 117, Folder 28)
  - NAI-NAT
    - Naitove, 1943-1960 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - National Business List, 1967-1968 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - National Mallinson Fabrics, 1942-1952 (Box 118, Folder 3-4)
    - National Container, 1951-1954 (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - National Silver Deposit Ware, 1948-1958 (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - National Urn Bag Co (includes strike materials--tea bags--see Box 119), 1941-1950 (Box 118, Folder 7-13)
  - NAT-NEW
    - National Urn Bag Co (see Box 118), 1948-1950 (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Nelson Bros., 1947-1950 (Box 119, Folder 2-3)
    - Neuwirth, 1963 (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Nevco (Amalgamated Local 5, materials in Spanish, on race relations), 1964-1965 (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - New American Library, 1960-1962 (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - Newark Electric (CIO #830), 1947-1950 (Box 119, Folder 7-8)
    - New Era Dental Laboratory, 1944-1950 (Box 119, Folder 9)
    - New Era Letter Company, 1959-1961 (Box 119, Folder 10)
    - New Haven Corrugated, undated (Box 119, Folder 11)
    - New York Air Valve, 1945-1949 (Box 119, Folder 12)
    - New York Ass'n of Wholesalers of Ladies & Children's Hats, 1943-1948 (Box 119, Folder 13)
    - New York Looseleaf, 1953 (Box 119, Folder 14)
    - New York Merchandise, 1946-1956 (Box 119, Folder 15-21)
  - NE-NU
    - NYMCO (New York Merchandise Company) (includes extensive strike materials), 1943-1958 (Box 120, Folder 1-6)
    - Northern Container, 1945-1953 (Box 120, Folder 7)
    - Noritake Co, 1962 (Box 120, Folder 8)
    - Novik & Co (includes strike materials), 1959-1965 (Box 120, Folder 9)
    - Noxall Buttons, 1937-1948 (Box 120, Folder 10)
    - Nurserie Togs, 1941-1964 (Box 120, Folder 11-13)
  - O-PA
    - Olian Bros, 1957-1962 (Box 121, Folder 1-2)
    - Oltarsh Fabrics, 1945-1958 (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - Olympic Knitwear, 1951-1961 (Box 121, Folder 4-5)